Almost heaven,
West Virginia
Blue Ridge Mountains
Shenandoah River
Life is old there,
older than the trees,
younger than the mountains
blowing like a breeze
country road
take me home
to the place
I belong
West Virginia
mountains mamma
take me home
country roads
All my memories
gather round her,
miner's lady,
stranger to blue water
Dark and dusty,
painted on the sky
misty taste of moonshine,
teardrop in my eye
country roads
take me home
to the place
I belong
West Virginia
mountain mamma
take me home
country roads
I hear her voice in the morning hour , she calls me
the radio reminds me of my home far away
And driving down the road I get a feeling that I should have been home
yesterday , yesterday
Country roads , take me home to the place I belong
West Virginia,
mountain mamma
take me home,
country roads
take me home
to the place
I belong
West Virginia
mountains mamma
take me home,
country roads,